Shenqi 1.0
Human Experiment 01.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Where is this?
Is this a dream?
We lack experimental data. so some
Shenqi investments have been halted.
Go and take a look.
-Investors stopped funding it
-Hang in there.
since we want human BCI experiments.
Hang in there.
We're so close.
Just need a human in the BCI.
We just need to enter the Shenqi world.
Shenqi 1.0
Human Experiment 01.
Shenqi Space is different
from the VR we know.
It's a new technology derived
from BCI research.
It was designed
to help people who became disabled
due to accidents
or suffered severe psychological trauma
to start a new life.
There's no problem with this.
The Shenqi Space we developed
is meant to be their new home.
It's based on a real-world model.
Real-time algorithms
simulate the real world.
Through data exchange. the simulation
replicates one's personality and memories.
Theoretically speaking.
you can start a new life
in the Shenqi Space.
That's just a concept.
If everyone chooses to escape life.
what's the point of this technology?
Have you conducted any experiments
or is this just a gimmick?
I heard your team's shutting down
due to a lack of funds.
A financing scam.
How do you ensure
information authenticity?
Calm down.
This is a dream.
It'll be fine after I wake up.
The pain felt so real.
This isn't a dream.
So where is this place?
Why am I here?
Wait.
My name is…
My leg…
I think I've been here before.
This feels…
very familiar.
Did I lose my memories?
If that happens every time.
what's controlling all of this?
It keeps happening.
The seagull is a signal
for the coming waves.
Then the shark will come.
What exactly is that?
A yacht is here.
Why didn't I see it before?
It's about time.
Hurry.
There's still time.
Help!
Is anybody there?
I found another Shenqi Beach sample.
When will you be back?
Don't worry. I'll be back soon.
We can't do what Li Qiang did.
Even a winner lost now. didn't she?
She injured her spine.
Whether she can stand again
depends on herself.
To conduct human experiments as planned.
we need money.
Trust me. I have a way.
Shenqi?
Beach Model.
The waves are coming soon.
Why are there no waves?
The pattern has changed.
What's going on?
I'm back to the start.
Beach Model.
Wait.
If
this was a human design.
then it makes sense.
A real shark wouldn't attack
people proactively.
If the yacht is the endpoint.
the shark is a predesigned obstacle.
If it's a human design.
it must have a pattern.
Just now.
it came from behind.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Five-second attack gap.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
I lose if I struggle with it
on the water's surface.
I can
try to swim deeper.
One.
Two.
Three.
No more than four seconds underwater.
Five seconds on the water's surface.
Three and a half seconds underwater.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
One.
Two.
Three.
One.
Two.
Three.
I don't have much stamina left.
To reach the yacht.
I need to swim about 80 meters.
I still have a chance.
Here it goes again.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
One.
Two.
Three.
Thirty more meters.
What's going on?
Why are there so many all of a sudden?
I can do this.
Five more meters.
I can't fail.
ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE R&D DIVISION
AM 9:30
Li Qiang.
How did this happen?
Wei Ran.
What's wrong?
Is Li Qiang crazy?
Access the lab's surveillance footage.
Open all the source code.
The acquisition
doesn't require Li Qiang's consent.
-Enough. you've gone on and on.
-Majority rules.
-Are you done?
-Problem solved. right?
Let's talk later.
What's more important
than the team being disbanded?
Hey.
What's going on?
Li Qiang is connected to the Shenqi BCI.
How did this happen?
Can't we wake her up?
Dr. Li's brain is very active now.
Intracranial temperature is at 42 degrees.
USER LOGIN
Are you done yet? Hurry up.
I got the surveillance footage.
This is from 8 a.m.
-We were in a meeting at this time.
-Yes.
Fast forward it.
Okay.
After the meeting.
no one was here except Dr. Li.
Turn on the experiment record.
Shenqi 1.0
Human Experiment 01.
DNA algorithm settings.
Environment: Beach.
Experiment: Surfing.
Start data recording.
Over.
So impulsive.
Why didn't we discuss this?
TEXTSTAY
Wei Ran. come here.
Look.
I checked all the BCI source code.
She's not in the Shenqi we developed.
Wait. if she's not in Shenqi.
then why is she connected to it?
The program has a loophole.
She's trapped in it.
I'm at the endpoint.
Why is there nothing here?
Is anybody here?
Who's driving the yacht?
Wei Ran. my leg.
I can't feel it.
I can't feel it anymore!
What's wrong with my leg?
This overwhelming feeling again…
I realize you're where the adventure is.
Isn't that what life's about?
Look forward. don't look back.
Keep going.
Stay conscious.
Don't fall here.
Wei Ran. I'm taking forest samples.
Don't worry. I found more beach samples.
This is my…
My…
memories.
Recording the fifth
forest sample collection.
Recording the 11th sky sample collection.
Recording the 16th wave sample collection.
Wei Ran.
Li Qiang!
Hang in there.
The doctor said
you severely injured your spine.
Get some rest.
You'll stand again.
No need to comfort me.
I'll handle my own affairs.
Bye.
Look at that lady.
-Do you need help?
-No. thank you.
I haven't told you something
while you were unconscious.
Our team
might get disbanded.
What happened?
Our investors withdrew their funding.
Further investment in Shenqi
has been halted due to
a lack of experimental time data.
To conduct experiments. we need money.
Let's take a stand
on how to proceed.
Investments are halted due to
a lack of actual experimental data.
But we're just a step away.
Let a human enter the BCI.
Just enter the Shenqi world
and do anything.
What a joke.
A human in the BCI is a big deal.
Security procedures are complex.
If we stop now.
we'll have spent seven years
building a bed.
I contacted Tata.
They're very interested in Shenqi.
No actual experiment data needed.
They think Shenqi can be
Tata's VR game merchandise
and promised to buy it.
Of course. all the staff are included.
You want to sell it?
I suggest we be more mature.
We must face reality.
What do you think?
Guys.
seven years ago.
Dr. Wei and I formed this team.
You all must remember the day
the original model was completed.
From the start. our research intention
was to play a role
in healthcare and education.
not simply catering to the VR games
the media keeps talking about.
We put so much effort into this.
To collect beach sample data.
I even sacrificed my legs.
-Li Qiang.
-So.
Shenqi isn't going anywhere.
Trust me.
I have a way.
Come on.
Let's get to work.
Dr. Li. I support you.
As the originator.
it's your right to keep it.
But you can't let everyone
starve with you for your ideals.
Over half of the team agrees
to the acquisition.
Think about it more.
TEXTSTAY
Shenqi 1.0
Human Experiment 01.
DNA algorithm settings.
Environment: Beach.
Experiment: Surfing.
Start data recording.
Over.
Signal preprocessing completed.
System module loading.
Spatial model generated.
Enable bio-brainwave signal detection.
EEG signal connection is stable.
Synchronizing data.
System module loading.
Spatial model generated.
Enable bio-brainwave signal detection.
Biosignal sampling in progress.
-We did it.
-Dr. Li. you're amazing.
-Right.
-Come on.
It's all thanks to Dr. Li.
-Great.
-This is the first ever experiment…
-We did it!
This will be a major breakthrough
in computer technology.
We carefully collected the samples.
-We must trust Li Qiang.
-It's a miracle.
-Yes. How is this possible?
-If not for her.
we wouldn't be here.
-Yes. that's true.
-That's right.
-Li Qiang.
-Listen.
From now on.
don't explore without saying a word.
I'll always be by your side
to help you realize your dream.
I even have a surprise.
Come with me.
This is all thanks to you.
How dare you say that?
Everyone deserves the credit.
-Let's drink up.
-Let's drink tonight.
-Drink more.
-Hurry. you two.
Here. cheers.
Dr. Wei. Dr. Li.
Here.
Enough. stop calling them
so formally in private.
No way.
You two are our team's backbone.
As if. You're just sitting on the fence.
Here. cheers.
-Here.
-Here. cheers.
Here. cheer up.
Why aren't you drinking?
-I drank it.
-Here.
Here. have one more.
How does it feel to be so loved?
The team members only care
about their own interests.
To you.
giving up on the R&D
means losing everything.
They don't care what you sacrificed.
They'll only remember
that you're disabled.
and that you can stand here again.
Isn't that wonderful?
Right?
The waves are coming.
What now?
What should I do?
There's no turning back.
I chose this path myself.
This is my own choice.
It's always been my choice.
I don't know how to explain
her brain's hyperactivity.
Intracranial temperature is at 43 degrees.
At this rate.
her brain will be fried to death.
I'll ask others for ideas.
Let's think. I'm sure there's another way.
Stop saying there are no traces.
Did you check Server 4?
We checked all eight servers.
No user information found.
If we stop now.
we'll have spent seven years
building a bed.
Trust me. I have a way.
I support you.
If I had known.
I wouldn't have said that.
Aren't we a team?
-Wu Li.
-Yes?
Wu Li. come.
About the forest module…
I'd like to ask for a favor.
Haven't we been doing R&D on BCI?
Something happened.
I asked a friend who's a professor.
He said this code suffix…
I tried everything.
This time. I'm certain
she's not in the Shenqi Space.
Li Qiang.
Where exactly are you?
Can you stop acting alone every time
and hurting yourself?
Gosh.
Don't worry.
I got the mountain sample.
I need more data.
-Dr. Wei.
Where did you go?
Look at this first.
I found another Shenqi Beach sample.
Just watch the ocean.
You're always struggling on your own.
Dr. Wei. if you keep making a fuss.
I won't take you anywhere again.
When you needed me the most.
I disappointed you.
-I think it's fine. you know.
-Wait.
Wait.
Don't we lack actual experimental data?
We can do it ourselves.
I know this is against the rules.
and it's very dangerous.
But if we don't risk it.
we won't have a chance.
What are we risking here?
People might die if we force it.
What if we don't wake up
or have mental problems after?
Can you take responsibility?
Enough. Dr. Wei.
It's not really a loss
to make and sell a bed.
We can't do what Li Qiang did.
She went without thinking.
Consider it a lesson for her.
-Jeez.
-What did you say?
Say that again!
-Enough.
-Don't meddle.
I've long wanted to quit.
You and Li Qiang make all the decisions.
When did you care about us?
Mr. Fan. we need your PIN.
74.
-Done.
-Okay.
Real-time monitoring synchronized.
All this hard work
can't prove anything.
Wei Ran must be so anxious now.
The acquisition
might be the best option.
I'm just a loser.
Wei Ran. you know me.
I made bad decisions
with a business mindset before.
But now. Li Qiang…
You have the most say here.
If this situation goes on.
we'll all become murderers.
You must…
I know.
Now. maybe we can only
disconnect her brain connection.
But her consciousness
will stay in the BCI forever.
leaving her in a vegetative state.
This is our best option now.
Move.
Activating the Shenqi program
would leave traces in the backend.
The AI command records…
show Li Qiang's data
in the BCI AI sequences.
and she seems to be speaking.
What is she saying?
I think she lost her memories.
Waves?
Sharks?
THERE'S STILL TIME. HELP! ANYBODY THERE?
SHENQI BEACH MODEL. THE WAVES ARE COMING.
I'M BACK TO THE START.
IF THIS WAS A HUMAN DESIGN…
IT HAS ITS OWN PATTERN. FIVE SECOND GAP.
Our Beach Model
didn't include giant waves or sharks.
That's why we couldn't find Li Qiang
in the Shenqi Space.
The two-way interaction
between her brain and the Shenqi algorithm
caused it to change.
creating a space we can't locate.
Can we find her
from the clue about the shark?
No. because we didn't create
a shark model.
She said a shark attacked.
so Shenqi didn't create the sharks.
She might have created them instead.
Wait. Does that mean she's become AI?
No.
Is that possible?
I'm not sure either.
Her brain unconsciously handled
some Shenqi calculations.
Is it her subconscious?
I've been observing her brain activity.
I can be sure
that Li Qiang's brain data
indeed resembles dreaming.
And she just injured her spine.
I suspect…
It's PTSD.
Right.
Let me try waking her up again.
Li Qiang.
What are you fixated on?
Look forward.
don't look back.
Use a virus.
It'll interfere with the AI.
In that case.
we'll lose all data
we've accumulated in the past seven years.
What's that sound?
Shenqi Space is infected
with a reverse algorithm virus.
The Shenqi AI code
should collapse in less than five minutes.
Shut down Shenqi AI's firewalls.
What's going on?
Why did it start to rain?
And why are the sharks in the ocean gone?
The Shenqi AI is broken.
Does that mean the sharks and waves
aren't part of the Shenqi world?
Hey. Li Qiang's brainwaves
suddenly became active.
She must've realized
she's not in the Shenqi Space.
Is the reverse algorithm complete?
Our AI has become useless.
She must get out of her subconscious.
Release the beacon virus to stimulate it.
Okay. Come on. get up.
Li Qiang. quickly realize
this is your subconscious space.
Why do I feel
the shark is coming?
In this world.
where should I go?
It's coming.
Where exactly should I go?
I've had enough!
What's that?
That's Shenqi's symbol.
-Hurry. move it.
-Quick.
Guys. her subconscious
is probably resisting the virus.
so I'll add another layer of code
on top of the virus
that Li Qiang can understand
to enhance her self-awareness.
-Got it.
-Okay. let's go.
Hurry.
What's going on?
They're gathering there.
Shenqi's beacon is drawing them in.
Almost there. just hang on a bit longer.
The rest is up to you.
What?
Isn't this the ugly duckling Wei Ran made?
I'm a huge coward.
I was brave once
and made a fantastic duckling boat.
Wei Ran's trying to help me.
It's over.
Wei Ran. look.
Shenqi's source codes are disappearing.
It's starting again.
Attacking the shark
actually backfires on me.
So I'm the one
blocking myself from getting out.
I wanted to prove too much
that even without my legs.
I can turn things around.
I didn't expect to slowly lose control.
My obsession. combined with AI.
became the sharks
and huge waves
that trapped me in the dream.
Here. I have healthy legs
and everything I lost in reality.
To get out.
there's only one key.
It's time to wake up.
-Why the black screens?
-I don't know…
She's awake.
Let's go.
Come on.
I've made arrangements
for Shenqi's press conference.
I…
I'll wait outside.
Wei Ran.
I'm sorry.
It's my bad.
I've made you worry.
Hello.
I'm Wu Li. the lead code engineer
of the Shenqi Development Team.
Welcome.
When we started R&D.
we hoped that Shenqi AI and the BCI
could usher in a new era
for medicine and education.
I'll tell you in detail
on behalf of Dr. Li Qiang.
Let's welcome Shenqi 2.0 together.
The press conference is so important.
Why didn't you go?
The experiment data you brought back
is more important.
I still miss my legs from the dream.
What?
Give me time.
I'll recreate the dream for you.
-What are you doing?
-Hold on tight.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-